and Christ is the light of the world
if salvation is in if you understand
salvation you will be able to live
lightened up you will be able to look at
this dark world and not allow the
darkness to depress you to overwhelm you
you will have let me say this way power
to lighten up how many of you would like
tower to lighten up beloved the glory
the Christ in you is the hope of glory
and it's very interesting because if you
look at Revelation chapter 14 verse six
and seven the Bible says that God's
people at the end of time are to go
forth with a message which says fear God
and what give glory when you're giving
glory what are you giving you're giving
what light because light is God's glory
so check the sagas you cannot give the
first angels message if you don't have
it you can't give God glory if you don't
have glory to give did you catch that
just now you cannot fulfill the first
angels message give glory to God if you
don't you can't give what you don't have
so in order to give glory to God in
order to give glory to God in the midst
of coronavirus and in the midst of of
mass shootings and in the midst of
calamities and in the midst of of a
world that seems to be growing darker
and darker by the day by the minute in
order to give glory to God you have to
have glory in you and the only way to
have glory in you is to have Christ the
hope of glory in you
so just lighten up lighten up